[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：JavaScript在语法上是C家族的成员。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: JavaScript is syntactically a member of the C family.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我们有标识符
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We've got identifiers which
可以从字母或下划线或美元符号开始。
can start with letters or underbars or dollar signs.
我建议不要以下划线或以下划线开始或结束您的属性名称
I recommend not starting or ending your property names with underbars or
美元符号，但它们似乎真的很受欢迎。
dollar signs, but they seem to be really popular.
美元符号被添加到语言中，以便于机器使用
Dollar sign was added to the language for the benefit of machines for
宏处理器和代码生成器，
macro processors and code generators,
希望能够创建名称的东西可以保证它们不会
things that wanted to be able to create names be guaranteed they wouldn't
与你的名字冲突，他们可以使用美元符号，这使他们安全。
conflict with your names that they could use a dollar sign and that made them safe.
不幸的是，一些孩子发现你可以有一个叫做美元的函数
Unfortunately, some kids found out that you could have a function called dollar
然后就疯狂了。
and went crazy with it.
所以，现在到处都是美元函数。
So, dollar functions are all over the place now.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我们有两种格式
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We have both formats for
做评论。
doing comments.
我建议只使用这些斜线格式，
I recommend using just these slashslash line format,
因为有时我们想使用注释来注释代码和
because sometimes we want to use comments for commenting out code and
正则表达式文字可以包含星形斜杠和斜杠。
regular expression literals can contain starslash and slashstar.
所以怪异可能会发生，
So weirdness can happen,
如果您使用的是块注释。
if you're using a block comments.
我们有与您期望在类C语言中看到的运算符相同的一组运算符。
We have the same set of operators that you would expect to see in a C-like language.
其中有几个工作方式略有不同，您需要了解这一点。
A few of them work a little bit differently that you need to be aware of.
语言中的一个大错误是加运算符既做加法又做加法
One big mistake in the language is that the plus operator does both addition and
串联。
concatenation.
这是JavaScript从Java中学到的一个坏习惯。
This is a bad habit JavaScript learn from Java.
在Java中，它并没有那么糟糕，因为它是强类型的。
In Java, it's not so bad, because it strongly typed.
所以，你可以预测它会做哪一个。
So, you can predict which one it's going to do.
JavaScript是松散类型的。
JavaScript is loosely typed.
所以直到你去做加号，它才会看操作数。
So it's not until you go to do the plus, there it looks at the operands.
如果它们都是数字，它会将它们相加，否则，
And if they're both numbers it'll add them, otherwise,
它会将它们都转换为字符串并将它们连接起来，这是不好的。
it'll convert them both into strings and concatenate them, which is bad.
例如，在Web应用程序中，
For example, in a web application,
当您要求用户在字段中键入数字时，您可能有一个表单域，
you might have a form field when you ask the user to type a number into the field,
然后你想把那个号码拿出来，再加上一些东西。
you then wanna take that number out and add to something.
忘记了从表单元素中获取的值总是
Forgetting that the value you take out of a form element is always
一个字符串，尽管它周围的一切都说，它是一个数字。
a string even though everything around it says, it's a number.
这真的是一个很大的困惑的来源，你不会得到一个错误，你只是得到
That's a really big source of confusion and you don't get an error you just get
极其恶劣的行为。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：所以，我们可以转换和
extremely bad behavior. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So, we can convert and
我们可以使用加酉运算符将字符串转换为数字。
we can use the plus unitary operator to convert strings into numbers.
所以，你经常想这样做是作为一种防御的事情。
And so, you often wanna do that is as a defensive thing.
如果你有一个值，你想要添加它，但你担心它可能不会
If you've got a value and you want to add it and you're concerned that it might not
是一个数字，你可以在做加法之前强制它是一个数字。
be a number, you can coerce it to be a number before you do the addition.
但如果你这样做了，我建议在它周围加上括号。
But if you do that, I recommend putting parens around it.
因为否则，你就会有两个相邻的加号，
Because otherwise, you end up with two plusses next to each other,
这看起来像是另一个问题。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我们
which can look like another problem. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We
没有正式的整数。
don't have integers formally.
因此可以使用除法运算符除两个整数，但是
So you can divide two integers using the divide operator, but
不能保证得到整数结果。
you're not guaranteed to get an integer result.
所以，你需要做好准备。
So, you need to be prepared for that.
因为它是二进制浮点，甚至浮点结果，你得到
And because it's binary floating point, even the floating point result, you get
可能不是你所期待的。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：百分比
might not be the one you would expect. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: The percent
符号运算符是余数运算符而不是模运算符，
sign operator is the remainder operator not the modulo operator,
这是一个遗憾，因为我认为模是更有用的。
which is a shame, because I think modulo is the more useful one.
不同之处在于哪一方签字
The difference is in which sign it
用途。&gt；&gt；演讲者1：我们已经谈过了
uses. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We already talked
关于双等和它的问题。
about double equal and the problems with it.
我建议你总是使用三重相等代替，只是因为有这样的
I recommend you always use triple equal instead, just because there are so
里面有很多奇怪的东西，是人们所期待的。
many weirdness in it, things that are expected.
YouTube上有一个叫Wat的迷因。
There's a meme on YouTube called WAT.
W-A-T
W-A-T.
有人看到Wat了吗？
Has anybody seen WAT?
是啊，这是一场闹剧。
Yeah, it's a crackup.
最主要的是，它在玩这个游戏。
And mostly, it's playing fun with this.
他们拿了两样东西，这两样差别很大，而且是它们的两倍
They take two things, which are wildly different and double equal them and
然后说，真的和他们去哪里？
then says, true and they go WAT?
他们会大笑一场。
And they get a big laugh.
所以，不要使用double equals。
So, don't use double equal.
逻辑AND运算符的工作方式与Java略有不同，
With the logical and operator works a little differently than it does in Java,
因为操作数不需要是金条，它们只需要是牛市。
because the operands do not need to be bullion, they only need to be bullish.
因此，如果第一个操作数为true，则结果是第二个操作数的值。
So if the first operand is truthy, the result is the value of the second operand.
否则，它是第一个操作数的结果。
Otherwise, it's the result of the first operand.
但是它确实做了短路，所以第二个操作数
It does do the short circuiting though, so the second operand
仅当第一个错误且符合逻辑或时才进行评估
will only be evaluated if the first one was faulty and logical or
工作方式类似。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：感叹号是
works in a similar way. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: The exclamation point is
逻辑NOT运算符，如果操作数为true，则结果为false。
the logical not operator, if the operand is truthy than the result is false.
否则，结果为真。
Otherwise, the result is true.
如果你有bang，bang两次，它会把看涨的值变成布尔值。
If you have bang, bang twice, it will turn a bullish value into a Boolean.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我们有按位运算符，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We have bitwise operators,
但我们没有INT
but we don't have ints.
所以工作的方式是我们采用64位的二进制浮点，
So the way that works is we'll take the 64-bit binary floating point,
将其转换为32位有符号整数。
turn it into a 32-bit signed integer.
对它做恶作剧，然后把它转换回来。
Do the nasty to it and then convert it back.
所以在一些语言中，你会看到人们在做转换，
So in some languages, you'll see people doing a shift,
因为他们认为它会比乘法快。
because they think it's gonna be faster than a multiply.
即使在那些语言中也不应该这样做，因为编译器足够聪明。
You shouldn't do that even in those languages, cuz compilers are smart enough.
你应该写你想写的东西，所以
You should write the thing that you intend, so
阅读程序的人会知道应该发生什么。
that someone reading the program will know what supposed to be happening.
编译器将挑选出最快的方法来做这件事。
The compiler will sort out the fastest way to do it.
但在这种语言中，绝对的，
But in this language, definitely,
你不能通过错误的方式来提高速度。
you're not getting speed improvement by doing it the wrong way.